pantherdb.org 2007-09-03

# SRI's Privacy Policy

SRI's Privacy Policy Effective 7/1/04 

SRI International (SRI) is a nonprofit organization that performs research and development activities for a broad range of customers. This Internet site (the "Site") is operated and maintained by SRI. 

SRI is committed to protecting your privacy and providing a safe and rewarding online experience. This Privacy Policy describes SRI's policies and procedures for the collection of personal information by this Site, and our use and dissemination of such information. **By visiting our Site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice**. 

**Information Collection and Use**

In general, our service automatically gathers certain usage information on our server logs including your IP address; what web page you've last visited; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system and platform; and the frequency of your visits to SRI.com. If you register on our site we may ask for your name, email address, company name, mailing address, and information about your interests and preferences. Once you register you are no longer anonymous to us. 

SRI may use this personal information to help customize the content that you see and to contact you about new technologies or product areas. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

SRI will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. 

SRI may send you unsolicited information, including email, unless you advise us during the registration process that you do not want to receive these types of correspondence from us. 

SRI has established and maintains reasonable procedures to protect the confidentiality, security, and integrity of personal information collected by this Site. SRI will disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process. 

SRI Privacy Policy Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. 

How to Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, our practices, or your dealings with SRI International, you can contact:

SRI International  
Attn: Office of the General Counsel  
333 Ravenswood Avenue  
Menlo Park, CA 94025  
(650) 859-2529

Email: [webmaster@sri.com](mailto:webmaster@sri.com)
